and today we are going to build a
python instagram bot this is because
this little one just opened her
instagram account and she has no
followers so using the power of python
and automation
we're going to try to make her
instafamous
let's get started
okay so here's the plan what our bot is
going to do
is that it's going to go to a hashtag of
instagram is going to like
photos on that hashtag he's also going
to comment
on those photos and then is going to go
to the profile
of the people posting those photos and
is going to follow them
if you don't know how automation works
on the browser it basically works with
something called
python and selenium selenium is a
project that allows you to basically
automate your browser so it's like a
google chrome
controlled by python thing is that it's
very easy to detect users that are using
selenium and instagram
is investing a lot of time in blocking
such people
but still i am going to try to implement
this bot using selenium
and if it doesn't work and if i get
blocked we're still going to try to do
the automation
using my android maybe you didn't know
this but it is possible
to send python commands to android you
can literally say
open up boom you can say take photo you
can say
tap here you can do all those things
from python to your android phone
so i'm gonna be doing all these tests
with a throwaway account with a
disposable account
in case i get blocked once i have all
that set up then
we're going to do it with the real
account all right so my bot is going to
login
into instagram we're going to dismiss
the popups then we're going to search
for a popular hashtag in this case bts
army
then we're going to scroll down a lot so
we can get a lot of photos
and then on each photo that we found
we're going to like
comment and follow the person who posted
the photo
now we're going to do this very fast and
very often
so hopefully we don't get blocked
[Music]
as you saw we just got blocked not
actually blocked we got rate
limited what that means is that
instagram told us that we're doing
things too fast so slow down
they don't know that we are about yet
what they know is that we are doing
things very fast so
i stopped the bot i changed the settings
a little bit and now it's gonna be even
slower we're going to follow and like
but we're going to wait like a minute or
a minute and a half
between actions so hopefully they're not
gonna tell us that we're doing things
too quickly
anymore funny enough the disposable
account that i created just to test this
thing
is already getting followers so that
means that this concept of
liking photo commenting and following
people works
we get following back it's already
working we go like two or three already
but today
it's fun in any ways i'm gonna keep
running this and we're going to see how
many follow back we get
from the bts army i didn't test this bot
with the beagle hashtag just because i
don't want to spam
that hashtag yet i want to spam this one
first now
what i'm going to do is still i'm going
to start to work on the bot
for our android phone so the robot is
going to open instagram we're going to
go
to the search and explore we tap on
search
then we paste the hashtag we select the
first hashtag
then we go to recent we tap the first
photo then we press
like then we go to comments we try to
comment but we will be blocked which is
okay
then we will follow the person who posts
to the hashtag
and then we repeat with the next photo
on the list
all right so as you just saw the bot is
working
pretty well we can automate our android
phone using python which is
awesome and it opens up my mind for so
many other ideas of
apps i can automate i am going to
increase the level of complexity
just a little bit and let me explain why
on the phone is very easy to tap here
tap there and all that stuff but it's
very hard to keep track of the photos
that i am liking and it's very hard to
find the photos to like because i have
to scroll
and i have to go back and scroll again
it's just very annoying it's very easy
to find the photos
on the browser so what i'm going to do
is i'm going to combine them both
on the browser i'm going to just get as
many photos as i can
and i'm going to get the urls of those
photos and then
i am going to open those urls on the
phone
and the android is going to open the
instagram application and on the
instagram application
i am going to be liking commenting and
following
all right so the browser we get the urls
and once we have a good amount
then we force open that on the phone and
on the phone with the process like
comment and follow all right
as you can see it works we can mix our
browser
with our android bot and now it's great
i can get the photos from my browser and
i can
force the app opening on my android
awesome stuff
so next step is to actually do this with
my doggies account which so far
has zero followers i already uploaded
some photos on my doggy's account to
make it look
natural let me show you how everything
looks like from the point of view of my
doggy
and i will see you once this is done
[Music]
so
okay so our bot has made some progress
and i think
i have good news but before we move on
to that i want to talk about
this as you can see i am wearing a
beautiful full stack
hoodie this is because we are launching
our normal colors 2020
merch this year we have full stacks
hoodie that's a full stack on the front
they have a coat on the back we also
have a bunch of new
and old stickers that people loved and
wanted to buy again
and we also have a nice notebook that
you can use to write down your goals
we wanted to do this merge because we
are celebrating also that we made 200
000 subscribers this year we wanted to
thank you for your support and your
appreciation
we really value you we appreciate you
and we don't take you for granted thank
you so much
for being here and also we wanted to
announce that
this is a non-profit project this merge
and all the profits from this merge are
going to be donated
to a doggy shelter here in south korea
so the link is in the description
so go and check it out all right and now
on to the results
this boat was running for less than 24
hours and we already have
100 followers which is not bad at all
i ran the bot very very slowly maybe
commenting on five
photos commenting on seven photos
following seven people
very very slowly but it looks like it
worked 24 hours
100 followers is not bad and i'm very
very surprised that it worked this well
it is true that it's hard to detect
bot activity on the phone but i
did get blocked i cannot comment anymore
and i haven't been able to comment since
last night
this morning i could comment again but
then again i got blocked so maybe
i am using the same text or i'm
commenting too quickly i still don't
know
but it looks like instagram has no
problem with me following
and liking people and liking photos as
much as i want
i was doing it really fast and nothing
happened but commenting
it looks like they are being careful
there 24 hours 100 followers
i'm happy and now you let me know what
you think on the comments
of this video do you want to see the
source code or would you like to see me
explain the source code i don't know
maybe that's boring but
you let me know on the comments thank
you so much for watching don't forget to
be happy
don't forget to eat kimchi don't forget
to check out the link remember we're
going to donate all the profits to a
doggy shelter
stay safe be happy bye
you